Why don't you come in?
你为什么不进来？
I don't want to disturb you in chat
我不想在聊天中打扰你
I brought you chicken rice
我给你带了鸡肉饭
Can you bring something else next time?
下次可以带点别的吗？
Don't you like this?
你不喜欢这个吗？
The taste will change
味道会变
how
如何
how's it going
怎么样了
Or an ordinary person
要么是一个普通人
Either an expert
要么是专家
Do you think
你认为
Does she know your identity?
她知道你的身份吗？
I hope so
但愿如此
worst degree
最坏的程度
you probably know everything
你可能什么都知道
So you still fell into the trap
所以你还是掉进了陷阱
Why do I feel this way?
为什么我有这样的感觉？
you have a great plan
你制定了一个伟大的计划
How is your leg injury?
腿伤怎么样了？
Skin injuries are easy
皮肤受伤很简单
you don't decide
你不决定
Go to the hospital for examination
去医院检查
it's time
是时候了
It's time to change medicine
是时候换药了
your sudden interest
你突然的兴趣
I'm not used to this
我不习惯这样
Didn't you close the door?
你没关门吗？
past?
过去？
you should feel pain now
你现在应该感到疼痛
presentable
体面的
Don't get pregnant in front of me
别在我面前怀孕
Why?
为什么？
I do not know you
我不认识你
you are so annoying
你真烦人
Don't you want to know?
你不想知道吗？
Huang Zicheng’s situation
黄子成的情况
Looks like he's having some problems
看起来他遇到了一些问题
Yaoyao admitted it
瑶瑶承认了
He said it was night fog
他说那是夜雾
always
总是
Why
为什么
She honestly confessed to Huang Zi
她诚实地向黄子表白
I have no idea
我不知道
I think Yaoyao is behind
我觉得瑶瑶背后
This must be a hidden secret
这一定是一个隐藏的秘密
Why do you think so?
你为什么这么认为？
When I was at the Viking Hotel
当我在维京酒店的时候
I saw she met a boy
我看到她认识一个男孩
I checked
我检查了
That young man’s name is Fang Lu
那个年轻人的名字叫方路
Feng Lu
冯璐
You didn't expect it?
你没想到吧
I just joined the group
我刚进群
They said you were looking for Chen Ting
他们说你在找陈婷
in her network
在她的关系网络中
Fang Lu
方璐
So I come to you
所以我来到你身边
Vice Mayor Fang Lu
方璐 副市长
Fang Yongping's son
方永平之子
How could Yaoyao know?
瑶瑶怎么也知道
So I said behind Yaoyao's back
所以我在瑶瑶背后说
must have
必须有
more secrets
更多秘密
Can't let her go easily
不能轻易放开她
Fang Lu, Yao Yao, Chen Ting
方璐、姚瑶、陈婷
relation
关系
Is he too?
他也是吗？
from the night fog
从夜雾中
You can't make a decision now
你现在无法做出决定
It would be great if it was Fang Lu
如果是方璐就好了
easy to say
说起来容易
what is he afraid of
他害怕什么
Ye Wu is not just colluding with Fang Lu
夜雾不只是与方路勾结
Chen Ting
陈婷
And the power is behind him
而权力就在他背后
I got you
我明白你的意思
this matter
这件事
may be related
可能有关系
Some government department officials
部分政府部门官员
According to relevant legal provisions
根据相关法律规定
Hotel of the month
本月酒店
signal tower
信号塔
is the opposite
是相反的
Cross the line
越界
High level of construction
建设水平高
not built
未建成
How did Zhao Jun get it?
赵军是怎么得到的呢？
approval procedure
审批程序
someone help him
有人帮助他
Does Zhao Jun know that he didn’t build it?
赵军知不知道他不是建的
He works in hotel development
他从事酒店开发工作
He must have known it wasn't built yet
他一定知道它还没有建成
It’s not easy for Zhao Jun
赵军不容易
approved
已获批准
behind this signal tower
在这个信号塔后面
This is a complex network of relationships
这是一个复杂的关系网络
You are just like Zhao Jun
你就像赵军一样
there are others
还有其他人
who copied
谁复制的
we should
我们应该
Clearly
清楚地
Tianyang, you are responsible for this matter
天阳，这件事你负责
Understood
明白了
Huang Zicheng’s temperament is also
黄子诚的气质也是
How is he now?
他现在怎么样了？
this time
这次
It was a big shock to him
对他来说是很大的震撼
Next let Huang Ziqing
接下来让黄子晴
Contact Yaoyao
与瑶瑶联系
and learn more about its hidden secrets
并了解更多关于它隐藏的秘密
amor
阿莫尔
In order to recover as soon as possible
为了尽快康复
OK
好的
Mr. Chen
陈先生
let me talk to him
让我跟他谈谈
Mind your limits
注意你的极限
Actually you don’t have to come with me
其实你不必跟我走
I'll go alone
我一个人去
Safe Zone Huang Zicheng
安全地带黄子成
I thank you
我感谢你
You are very polite
你很有礼貌
I have no idea
我不知道
How should I speak?
我该怎么说话？
this is work
这是工作
this is normal
这是正常的
I'll treat you to dinner another day
改天我请你吃饭
Don't eat in bars
不要在酒吧吃饭
Huang Zicheng and I have a date
我和黄子成有个约会
I won't go with you
我不会和你一起去
no problem
没问题
If your doctor tells you to stay in the hospital
如果您的医生告诉您留在医院
Everything is under the doctor's arrangement
一切都在医生的安排下
What's the difference between you and me?
你和我有什么区别？
you are right
你是对的
Yaoyao is a spy
瑶瑶是间谍
That's how it feels
就是这样的感觉
of course not
当然不是
in the past
在过去
country to me
国家对于我来说
for me
为我
but this time
但这一次
When you're on a limited path
当你走在有限的道路上时
I saw Sister Shi
我看见施姐了
at that moment
在那一刻
This concept suddenly appeared
这个概念突然出现
It seems that I have become
看来我已经成为了
I have confidence
我有信心
I won't be alone
我不会孤单
It seems that I suddenly
看来我突然
I know you
我知道你
At work, persevere
工作中，坚持不懈
National Security
国家安全
protect the integrity of the country
保护国家的完整
food is ready
食物准备好了
It's time to eat
吃饭时间到了
I am coming
我来了
let's go
我们走吧
honestly
诚实地
They are really cruel
他们真的很残忍
this is the first time
这是第一次
when i face my real fears
当我面对真正的恐惧时
if you were me
如果你是我
i will kill them
我会杀了他们
But Lao Huang is here too
不过老黄也在
How can I get him involved?
我怎样才能让他参与进来？
At that moment I was about to collapse
那一刻我快要崩溃了
War is not a game
战争不是游戏
Cruelty is the truth
残酷才是真相
Understood
明白了
this place
这个地方
I brought Yaoyao here before
我之前带瑶瑶来过这里
I'm thinking now
我现在在想
They may all be visible
它们可能都是可见的
Didn't you tell them?
你没告诉他们吗？
we start to intervene
我们开始介入
I'm not that stupid
我没那么傻
struggle
斗争
Who reveals his or her identity first?
谁先暴露自己的身份
Who will lose?
谁会输？
our relationship
我们的关系
at first
起初
About lies
关于谎言
No matter which side is revealed
无论哪一面被揭露
The result will be very bad
结果会很糟糕
What do you think of our relationship?
你觉得我们的关系
Will there be good results?
会有好的结果吗？
in battle
战斗中
Emotions are the victims
情绪本来就是受害者
The more you fall, the more dangerous you are
摔得越多，就越危险
Let me talk about feelings with you
我和你谈感情
you're talking to me about work
你在跟我谈论工作
Brother, can you be more harmonious?
兄弟你能和谐一点吗？
You know why I always tell you
你知道为什么我总是告诉你
Didn't you do a good job?
你没做的好吗？
Do you know why
你知道为什么吗
are you single
你单身吗
Are you quarreling?
你们在吵架吗？
Do you still feel uncomfortable?
你还觉得不舒服吗？
after everything
在每件事之后
You were beaten because of me
你为了我被打了
but you don't know
但你不知道
What kind of person is she
她是一个什么样的人
Maybe act with you
也许和你一起行动
like a series
就像一个系列
what do you like
你喜欢什么
Only characters in this series
仅此系列中的角色
not an actor
不是演员
she is always playing
她总是在玩
your favorite character
你喜欢的角色
make
使
He makes you love her
他让你爱她
maybe in this world
也许在这个世界上
in this world
在这世上
This guy Yaoyao
瑶瑶这家伙
Even the name is fake
连名字都是假的
"Gao Tianyang."
“高天阳。”
i found you
我发现你
in the realm of private love
在私人爱情领域
you have great experience
你有很好的经验
I believe
我相信
no one can help you
没有人可以帮助你
I can only endure it myself
只能自己忍着
Since you have chosen
既然你选择了
this battle
这场战斗
you have to overcome this difficulty
你必须克服这个困难
Do you think this is a sacrifice?
你认为这是一种牺牲吗？
does it worth?
值得吗？
in my eyes
在我眼里
this is not a sacrifice
这不是牺牲
You want me to play games like you
你想让我像你一样玩游戏
as a programmer
作为一名程序员
How much will you give me
你会给我多少钱
i don't want to do that
我不想那样做
I'm not interested
我对此不感兴趣
no motive
没有动机
If you want me to be Duane
如果你想让我成为杜安
even if i have no money
即使我没有钱
I'm willing to do this
我愿意这样做
even though
即使
for him
为了他
I don't think it's a sacrifice
我认为这不是牺牲
I can overcome it too
我也能克服
I can sacrifice for my country
我可以为国家牺牲
but i don't believe it
但我不相信
A person can give up
一个人可以放弃
his feelings
他的感受
Humans are emotional animals
人是情感动物
I'm not saying give up on feelings
我并不是说放弃感情
but give up freedom
而是放弃自由
Give up your happiness and sadness
放弃你的快乐和悲伤
But you close yourself
而你却封闭自己
Give up being an ordinary person
放弃做一个普通人
Guoan has not abandoned humanity
国安并没有抛弃人性
This is not an abandonment of humanity
这并不是对人性的抛弃
But control desire
而是控制欲望
you have to remind yourself
你必须提醒自己
Don’t make the mistake of talking while drunk
不要犯酒后说话的错误
you can't speak without restrictions
你不能不受限制地说话
you can't relax
你不能放松
you can't do whatever you want
你不能为所欲为
Because the opponent is always in darkness
因为对手随时都处于黑暗之中
in the darkness
在黑暗中
hard
难的
very difficult
非常困难
"Gao Tianyang."
“高天阳。”
I sympathize with you
我很同情你
presentable
体面的
You will get used to it
你会习惯的
i'm making fun of you
我在取笑你
I didn't hear
我没听到
Understood
明白了
this is not
这不是
I think of private workers
我想到的私营工人
Don't you believe it?
你不相信吗？
I can do it
我能做到
I trust you
我相信你
I just don't want to see
我只是不想看到
accept this pain
接受这种痛苦
You could have
本来你可以
You live a carefree life
你生活无忧无虑
Is not this contradictory?
这不是自相矛盾吗？
As long as you can overcome this pain
只要你能克服这种痛苦
you will become stronger
你会变得更强
So you think I can come back
所以你认为我可以回来
Continue to investigate Yaoyao
继续调查瑶瑶
There is no murmur in his heart
他的心里没有一丝杂音
no feeling
没有任何感觉
At least don't let these feelings go away
至少不要让这些感觉消失
affect your judgment
影响你的判断
i will try my best
我会尽力而为
I don't try
我不尝试
but guaranteed
但有保证
Okay, I'll try my best to control it
好的，我会尽力控制的
This is just the beginning
这仅仅是个开始
there's still a long way to go
还有很长的路要走
I just hope you don't give up
我只希望你不要放弃
Hello
你好
Tian Yang
田阳
Zhao Jun did not show up
赵军没有出现
appear in company
出现在公司
Understood
明白了
wait me back
等我回来
eat quickly
快点吃
It's cold
是冷的
eat more
多吃一点
Zhao Jun is on a business trip in the afternoon
赵军下午出差了
Maybe Homeland Security
也许是国土安全局
Can't find it yet
暂时找不到
This time it seems to be the National Security Bureau
这次好像是国安
he won't give up
他不会放弃
Planning Department
规划处
Do you have any questions
你有问题吗
The planning bureau can handle it
规划局可以处理
Someone will bear it
会有人来承受
The most important thing now is Zhao Jun
现在最重要的是赵军
Can you withstand Guo An's investigation?
你能承受郭安的调查吗？
I know
我知道
As for Zhao Jun
至于赵军
I'll take care of it
我会处理的
I will try my best to make everything go smoothly
我会尽力让一切顺利
It ends here
到此结束
Now the Office of National Security
现为国家安全办公室
can you think of a way
你能想个办法吗
stop investigation
停止调查
I've gone beyond
我已经逾越了
Nature
自然的
Where is the leadership?
领导在哪里？
Mayor, you haven't left yet
市长你还没走呢
Enter.
进入。
close the door
关门
I heard there is
我听说有
Investigate illegal cases
查处违法案件
what happened
发生了什么
Ono Hotel
小野宾馆
in the signal tower
在信号塔里
I found a camera at the top
我在顶部发现了一个摄像头
they knock on the door
他们敲门
Opposite the military base
军事基地对面
Who approved it?
谁批准的？
Planning Department
规划处
Did you say hello?
你打招呼了吗？
stupid
愚蠢的
I really do not know
我真的不知道
they arrange cameras
他们安排相机
They think the signal tower
他们认为信号塔
Have I found you?
我找到你了吗？
No
不
Someone will be responsible for the planning office
会有人承担策划办公室
At most it's legal punishment
顶多是法律的惩罚
I'm scared now
我现在害怕
The National Security Bureau won't release him
国安局不释放他
The hotel owner’s name is Zhao Jun
酒店老板叫赵军
Now the Office of National Security
现为国家安全办公室
He started interrogating him
他开始审问他
Do not communicate with the following people
不与以下人员交流
with these founders
和这些创始人一起
Things are different now
现在情况不同了
Yes
是的
There is a problem with national security
国安有问题
Can I solve the problem?
我能解决问题吗？
Can be solved
可以解决
allow
允许
go
去
I'll ask later
我稍后再问
Tian Yang
田阳
We went to Zhaojun Company
我们去了昭君公司
He didn't go to work all day
他一整天都没有去上班
The secretary said he was on a business trip
秘书说他出差了
Where did he go?
他去哪了？
I have no idea
我不知道
Do you see it at home?
你在家里看到了吗？
Pony is watching over there
小马在那边看着
No one is back now
现在没有人回来
Ask the second group to observe
请第二组观察
I'm going to the planning office tomorrow
我明天要去规划办公室
see what happens
看看会发生什么
Zhao Jun
赵军
Once there is news
一旦有消息
notify me immediately
立即通知我
Understood
明白了
its strong
其强者
He went to the company again
他又去了公司
Go to work first
先去上班吧
Can I rest assured?
我可以放心吗？
national security office
国家安全办公室
This is not the tax office
这不是税务局
tell me
告诉我
Is this dangerous?
这危险吗？
Don't worry
不用担心
It's none of your business
这不关你的事
at first
起初
It's not my turn yet
还没轮到我
you used my place
你用了我的地方
Only build signal towers
只建信号塔
besides it
此外它
I asked someone to approve it
我请人批准了
Yes or no
是不是
if they ask me again
如果他们再问我
i will tell the truth
我会说实话
National Security Office Thunder
国安办雷霆
I can not stand it any more
我受不了了
I didn't ask you to bear it
我没有要求你承受
stay here for a few days
在这里住几天
I'll take care of it
我会处理的
I will tell you
我会告诉你
fully understand
完全了解
Hi pretty girl
你好美女
How did you get your hand injured?
你的手是怎么受伤的？
we are separated
我们分开了
This is the so-called water of forgetfulness
这就是所谓的健忘之水
This is for you
这是给您的
her hand is hurt
她的手受伤了
Is it okay to give her wine?
给她酒可以吗？
One cup of forgetful water per person
健忘水每人一杯
Can you forget it after drinking?
喝完酒就能忘记吗？
i really hope
我真的希望
Back to original
回到最初
The result is still the same
结果还是一样
Let's go talk somewhere else
我们去别的地方聊吧
This is for you
这是给您的
Anti-alcohol
抗酒精
Thanks
谢谢
Thank you for staying in the hospital
谢谢你留在医院
Stay with me for two days
陪我住两天
Don't do this again next time
下次不要再这样做
I'm not always so lucky
我不是每次都那么幸运
I didn't think much about it at the time
我当时没想太多
I'm worried you'll get hurt
我担心你会受伤
No matter how others hurt me
无论别人如何伤害我
it won't hurt me too much
它不会伤害我太多
Their mission is mine
他们的使命就是我的
That is
那是
Play a special game with you
和你玩一个特别的游戏
But our experience is real
但我们的经历是真实的
I can leave too
我也可以离开
But I'm back to see you again
但我又回来看你了
in fact
事实上
That day at the casino
那天在赌场
I have thought about this problem
我想过这个问题
i want to tell you
我想告诉你
to be honest
说实话
if you really want to tell me
如果你真的想告诉我
the truth
真相
No need to gamble
没必要去赌博
can decide
可以决定
but if i tell you
但如果我告诉你
perhaps
或许
Accompany you to surrender
陪你去投降
I'm really afraid of going to jail
我真的很害怕坐牢
so
所以
I used a bet
我用了一个赌注
Help you make a decision
帮助您做出决定
I know it's cowardly
我知道这很懦弱
Why are you a spy?
你为什么是间谍？
My parents died young
我的父母很早就去世了
And my family conditions are not good either.
而且我的家庭条件也不好
since childhood
从小时候起
My sister works part time
我姐姐做兼职
I am responsible for studying
我负责学习
until one day
直到有一天
my colleague told me
我的同事告诉我
play this game
玩这个游戏
you can make a lot of money
你可以赚很多钱
I'm curious
我感到好奇
so follow them
所以跟随他们
Play game together
一起玩游戏
Even on the day of the mission
即使在执行任务的当天
come down
下来
Get down immediately
立即趴下
raise your hand
举起你的手
put your hand in my sight
把你的手放在我的视线里
Get down immediately
立即趴下
come down
下来
All right
好吧
go out
出去
We received a report
我们收到一份报告
You are suspected of possessing illegal weapons
您涉嫌持有非法武器
What?
什么？
it's out of the question
这是不可能的
open this box
打开这个盒子
Open
打开
I always
我一直
explain it to them
向他们解释一下
I'm just playing games
我只是在玩游戏
I have no idea
我不知道
I don't know at all
我根本不知道
Where did the gun come from?
枪从哪里来？
But they just asked me
但他们只是问我
Is the car mine?
车是我的吗？
We need to deliver the gun
我们要把枪送到
No. 9772 Olympic Street
奥林匹克街9772号
This is the address
这是地址
The weird thing is
奇怪的是
the address they mentioned
他们提到的地址
This is the mission of the game
这是游戏的使命
trading locations
交货地点
I can only keep telling them
我只能不断地告诉他们
it's just a game
这只是一个游戏
I asked them
我问他们
They used my phone to check
他们用我的手机来检查
but on my phone
但在我的手机上
in my phone
在我的手机里
she disappeared
她消失了
police told me
警察告诉我
People who receive this address
收到此地址的人
I admit
我承认
I bought the weapons myself
武器是我自己买的
on my phone
在我的手机上
in my phone
在我的手机里
Record your contact information with him
记录你和他的联系方式
All the evidence at the time
当时的所有证据
Refers
指的是
Know
知道
i was cheated
我被骗了
There must be something wrong with this game
这游戏肯定有问题
i live in that room
我住在那个房间里
in that room
在那个房间里
I realized later
我后来才意识到
The girl smuggled drugs
那个女孩走私毒品
white girl killed
白人女孩被杀
black aunt
黑阿姨
He is a thieving criminal
他是一个偷窃的罪犯
those days
那些日子
every day
每天
I dare not sleep
我不敢睡觉
when i fall asleep
当我睡着的时候
I had a lot of nightmares
我做了很多噩梦
until one day,
直到有一天，
The jailer told me
狱卒告诉我的
It turns out someone recognized me.
原来有人认出了我。
I went crazy
我当时就疯了
I'm jailbroken
我越狱了
I do not want
我不想要
Go back to that place.
回到那个地方。
He asked me to call him Mr. Yu
他让我叫他于先生
sit.
坐。
I can help you get rid of the guilt
我可以帮助你摆脱负罪感
but there is a condition
但有一个条件
any conditions
任何条件
keep playing
继续玩
I can't play anymore
我不能再玩了
game let me
游戏让我
in this case
在这种情况下
it seems
它似乎
you prefer prison
你更喜欢监狱
Why did you involve me?
你为什么把我牵扯进来？
We need your help
我们需要你的帮助
What do you need me to do?
你需要我做什么？
Go back to school and study hard
回到学校好好学习
keep playing
继续玩
follow me
跟我来
a person who plays games
一个玩游戏的人
This is the second generation government
这是第二代政府
This is the second time we've done this
这是我们第二次这样做
People we met at the hotel
我们在酒店遇到的人
Of course someone will come to save him
自然会有人来救他
but i'm different
但我不一样
No one helped me at all
根本没有人帮助我
So then
那么那么
I agree with that deal
我同意那笔交易
as i expected
正如我所料
after a while
一段时间后
Break all recognition
打破一切认可
He said he deliberately accused me
他说他故意指责我
The way to communicate is to find hackers
沟通的方式就是寻找黑客
intentionally
故意地
My gun is in my car
我的枪在我的车里
exist
在
Unknown status
状况不明
it is placed inside
它被放置在里面
Because there is not enough evidence
因为证据不够
I was acquitted
我被无罪释放
I asked Mr. Yu
我问于先生
who is he
他是谁
he tells me
他对我说
they are an information organization
他们是一个信息组织
They collected all the information
他们收集了所有的信息
The name of the organization is "Night Mist"
该组织的名称是“夜雾”
The homework they sent me
他们发给我的作业
this is a survey
这是一项调查
What kind of players can they develop into?
他们可以培养成什么样的球员
Then he asked me to report
然后他让我汇报
I give them all the content
我给他们所有的内容
Will choose night mist
将选择夜雾
Some players will be selected
部分球员将被选中
He asked me to take them to the game
他让我带他们去看比赛
So I came to Tianhai
于是我来到了天海
according to their requirements
根据他们的要求
Who asked for them?
谁要求他们的？
and become your partner
并成为您的合作伙伴
At that time you were like
那时的你就像
Like the straw that saved me
就像救了我的稻草一样
i have to catch you
我必须抓住你
Because I promised
因为我答应过
if they let you
如果他们让你
Join the game
参加游戏
They won't take advantage of my family.
他们不会利用我的家人
force
强迫
Do anything
做任何事
.then I can finish the game
.然后我就可以完成游戏了
I'm leaving Jin Hye
我要离开金惠了
Do you believe what they say?
你相信他们说的话吗？
I have no idea
我不知道
I really don't want to go to jail
我真的不想进监狱
I dare not resist
我不敢反抗
I don't believe them
我不相信他们
i can't believe you
我不敢相信你
You almost killed my father
你差点杀了我父亲
He also hurt his family
还伤害了家人
Is this your usual trick?
这是你惯用的伎俩吗？
sorry
对不起
I really do not know
我真的不知道
they are taking advantage of your family
他们正在利用你的家人
to threaten you
来威胁你
I regretted it very much at that moment
那一刻我非常后悔
because I know
因为我知道
Lonely
孤独
How terrible
多可怕啊
I was just thinking
我刚在想
I can't leave you alone
我不能丢下你一个人
alone
独自的
I'll let you face them alone
我会让你独自面对他们
Because it's very dangerous
因为这是非常危险的
I don't want you to be
我不想让你成为
I am the second
我是第二个
I'm scared every day
我每天都很害怕
helpless
无助
and fear
和恐惧
so i'm back
所以我回来了
I explain it all to you
我向你解释这一切
not for
不是为了
explain myself
解释一下我自己
I just want to tell you
我只想告诉你
to be honest
说实话
That's it
就是这样
do you know
你知道吗
future?
将来？
I know
我知道
us
我们
we will complete our mission
我们将完成使命
you will face
你将面临
by the National Security Office
由国家安全办公室
Is this the life you want?
这是你想要的生活吗？
I only know
我只知道
i can't leave
我不能离开
I can't leave you alone
我不能丢下你一个人
There
那里
Although I
虽然我
I work for Ye Wu
我为夜雾工作
But I hate them as much as you do
但我和你一样讨厌他们
Because at the beginning
因为一开始
at the beginning
在一开始的时候
probably now
大概现在
how he hurt you
他如何伤害你
Understood
明白了
if
如果
will you forgive me?
你会原谅我吗？
I have no idea
我不知道
i need time to think
我需要时间思考
The same to you
你也是
think carefully
好好想想
Do you give up?
你放弃吗？
hard freedom
硬自由
It doesn't matter
没关系
Ordinary people don't know
普通人不知道
Before going to Macau
去澳门之前
Did Gao Tianyang tell you?
高天阳告诉你了吗？
No
不
How did you know?
你怎么知道的？
tell me about the nurse station
告诉我护士站
Are you pretending?
你在假装吗？
I'm mad
我疯了
I'm pretending here
我在这里假装
Are all the people who come to the hospital sick?
来医院的人都生病了吗？
You've been stopped by spies
你被间谍拦住了
I'm still arrogant
我依然傲慢
you are like this
你是这样的
Go to Macau for me
还替我去澳门
To save me from the fire
为了救我脱离火海
honestly
诚实地
I'm very impressed
我印象很深刻
What does this mean to you?
这对你来说意味着什么？
I am for the country
我是为了国家
Do not think too much
不要想太多
Understood
明白了
seventh bed
第七张床
Getting ready to clean the floor on the third floor
准备去三楼清理地板
OK
好的
Where did you buy the wheelchair?
你从哪里买的轮椅？
I rented it in the basement of the hospital
我在医院的地下室租的
I can walk by myself
我可以自己走路
The doctor said
医生说
I'm recovering well
我恢复得很好
I can be discharged from the hospital in two days
两天后我就可以出院了
This is not a simple wheelchair
这不是一个简单的轮椅
This is my apology to Sister Shi
这是我给石姐的道歉
and respect
和尊重
I believe
我相信
This is the curse you gave me
这是你给我的诅咒
This is better
这个更好
Your feet look like this
你的脚是这样的
Replacement goes to Macau
换人去澳门
Isn't that all?
这还不是全部吗？
You are my own choice
你是我自己选择的
i must protect you
我必须保护你
besides it
此外它
I promised your brother
我答应过你哥哥
to protect you
为了保护你
it seems
它似乎
My brother is very important to you
我哥哥对你来说很重要
Stop talking nonsense
别废话了
let's talk about work
我们来谈谈工作吧
What did Yaoyao say?
瑶瑶说了什么？
Yaoyao said
瑶瑶说
Players who have played games with it
用它玩过游戏的玩家
I am playing game
我玩游戏
This is the second generation government
这是第二代政府
Have you seen this hotel before
你以前见过这家酒店
Is his name Fang Lu?
他叫方路吗？
Yes
是的
This is it
就是这个
Fang Lu
方璐
fully understand
完全了解
become
变得
Can you
你可以吗
answer me a question
回答我一个问题
What?
什么？
Do you think?
你认为？
What Yaoyao said is true
瑶瑶说的是真的
what do you think?
你怎么认为？
I have no idea
我不知道
Do you believe
你相信吗
What she said is true
她说的是真的
except me
除了我
I trust your judgment more
我更相信你的判断
i can't answer you
我无法回答你
I need to investigate to make a judgment
我需要调查以便做出判断
but we need
但我们需要
Continue to cooperate with Yaoyao
继续与瑶瑶合作
Investigate the details of Yaoyao
调查瑶瑶的详细情况
Especially her relationship with Fang Lu
尤其是她和方璐的关系
we must know
我们必须知道
Fang Lu’s status in the game
方璐在游戏中的状态
Except Yaoyao
除了瑶瑶
does he have
他是否有
Any other contact details
任何其他联系方式
or partner
或合作伙伴
Are we partners?
我们是合作伙伴吗？
Or our opponent?
还是我们的对手？
Yes
是的
This is it
就是这个
complicated
复杂的
say
说话
What can't I ask?
我不能问什么？
become
变得
tell me
告诉我
In the private world of workers
在工人的私人世界里
In a world of private workers?
在私人工人的世界里？
nature
自然
who has no feelings
谁没有感情
but
但
hard to have
很难拥有
we don't care about anything
我们什么都不关心
Because why แบก is not
因为什么แบก不
This is the country's mission
这是国家的使命
Know
知道
no matter what happens
无论发生什么
from
从
Can not accept
无法接受
you did well
你做得好
honestly
诚实地
your performance
你的表现
better than i expected
比我预期的要好
if
如果
I mean if
我的意思是如果
What about Yaoyao?
瑶瑶呢
Everything she said is true
她说的都是真的
Already framed
已经被框起来了
is forced
是被迫的
But now I regret it
但现在我后悔了
Can she still be saved?
她还能得救吗？
Do you still want to save her?
你还想救她吗？
I believe I can save someone
我相信能拯救一个人
more important than arresting someone
比逮捕某人更重要
Did I say something wrong?
我说错什么了吗？
Yes
是的
I believe what you say
我相信你的话
Very logical
很有逻辑性
but you must remember
但你必须记住
maintain your image
维护你的形象
don't do anything
不要做任何事
anything beyond your design
任何超出你设计的东西
other problems
其他问题
We will help you solve it
我们会帮您解决
As for Yaoyao
至于瑶瑶
what did i give you
我给了你什么
Must verify
必须验证
you must be conscious
你必须有意识
if you want to save her
如果你想救她
She can't lie to you anymore
她不能再骗你了
I remember
我记得
Didn't you delete your number?
你没删号码吗？
What is a fake corpse?
什么是假尸？
things have changed
情况已经改变
Life is re-planned
生活被重新规划
almost
几乎
allow
允许
I'll give you the tools
我会给你工具
no need
没有必要
all these external things
所有这些外在的东西
I'm looking for you now
我现在正在找你
I have more important things
我有更重要的事情
What?
什么？
Help me find someone
帮我找人
Are you looking for someone else?
你在找别人吗？
My partner from the last game
上一场比赛中我的搭档
I need more information
我需要更多信息
any information
任何信息
For example its calculation
例如它的计算
password
密码
If I had her account password
如果我有她的账号密码
I still need you
我还需要你
How did you get into her game?
你是怎么进入她的游戏的？
haven't discovered it yet
还没发现它
therefore
因此
I will sell digital decompilers
我会卖数字反编译器
via her computer or mobile phone
通过她的电脑或手机
There is a game log
有游戏日志
Why do I feel this way?
为什么我有这样的感觉？
you can't fix it
你无法解决它
Just want to sell me
只想卖掉我
digital decoding program
数字解码程序
I'll give you an idea
我给你一个主意
I'm not forced to buy them
我没有被迫购买它们
I can't write a program to decode that number
我不会编写程序来解码该数字
I do not need you
我不需要你
You are very busy
你很忙
I tried it, it helped
我试过了，有帮助
I trust you
我相信你
I will email you later
我稍后会发电子邮件给您
OK
好的
I have no money
我没钱
he was first convicted
他首先被定罪
Do not make money
不赚钱
Do I want your money?
我要你的钱吗？
There is true love in the world
世上有真情实感
give me a car
给我一辆车
What
什么
process
过程
I didn't tell her
我没有告诉她
About our separation
关于我们的分离
Understood
明白了
sit
坐
Is there any problem with Huitianhai?
回天海有问题吗？
If you don't bother me there won't be a problem
如果你不打扰我就不会有问题
You will adapt to your new identity
你将适应你的新身份
What is the new mission?
新的使命是什么？
Working at Jihai Biological Group
就职于集海生物集团
my father is there
我父亲在那里
correct
正确的
Didn't you promise me?
你不是答应我了吗？
Don't get my father involved.
别把我父亲卷入其中
If you enter
如果您输入
You won't have anything to do with him
你不会和他有任何瓜葛
How could I not influence him?
我怎么能不影响他呢？
So you must be careful
所以你一定要小心
don't cause any trouble
别惹任何麻烦
Do not disturb Mr. Huang
请勿打扰黄先生
My father didn't run that company.
我父亲没有经营那家公司
I have no intention of entering
我无意进入
Enter
进入
nature
自然
I will give you time
我会给你时间
With Mr. Huang
与黄先生
In addition to your major
除了你的专业之外
Enter the Internet section
进入互联网部分
it's not difficult
这并不难
There is a Yaoyao who can help you
有一个瑶瑶可以帮助你
How did you apply for employment?
您是如何申请就业的？
she has a great method
她有一个很棒的方法
Yes or no
是不是
What’s wrong with you
你怎么了
What's up with her?
她怎么了？
I have to ask you
我得问你
I gonna go see
我去看看